A Guide to the Records of T. Marshall Hahn Jr, 1962-1974
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series V, 1970-1972
  - S Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1852)
  - Salaries, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1853)
  - Savage, Lon K., 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1854)
  - Scholarships and Grants, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1855)
  - Scholarships and Grants #2, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1856)
  - Scholarships and Grants #3, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1857)
  - (SDS) Students for a Democratic Society, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1858)
  - Security, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1859)
  - Sociology, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1860)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1861)
  - Southern Regional Education Board (SREB), 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1862)
  - Space Allocations, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1863)
  - Speaking Engagements, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1864)
  - Sporn Award, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1865)
  - Staff Meetings, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1866)
  - State Council of Higher Education #1, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1867)
  - State Council of Higher Education #2, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1868)
  - State Council of Higher Education (#2 beginning Sept), 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1869)
  - Statistics, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1870)
  - Student Budget Board, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1871)
  - Students Forums Board, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1872)
  - Student Government Association, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1873)
  - Student Government Association (file #2, beginning June 1970), 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1874)
  - Student Housing, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1875)
  - Student Affairs Dean Al Payne, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1876)
  - Student Letters- Others, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1877)
  - Student Letters- Others #2 Beginning Sept 1970, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1878)
  - Student Letters- To and From, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1879)
  - Student Organizations, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1880)
  - Student Publications Board, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1881)
  - Student Residence Program Dean Martha Harder, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1882)
  - Student Services- Dean J. Gordon Brown, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1883)
  - Student Union, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1884)
  - Subscriptions, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1885)
  - Summer School Programs, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1886)
  - Tech Festival, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1887)
  - T.I.A.A., 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1888)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1889)
  - Treasurer- J. F. Boone, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1890)
  - T.R.W., 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1891)
  - University Council #1, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1892)
  - University Council #2, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1893)
  - University Council #3, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1894)
  - University Council #3 cont., 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1895)
  - University Council #4, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1896)
  - University Professorship, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1897)
  - University Services and Auxiliary Enterprises - Mr H.W. Swink Dir., 1970 (Box 53, Folder 1898)
  - Upward Bound, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 1899)
  - V Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 1900)
  - Va. Dept. of Agriculture, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 1901)
  - Veterinary Science, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 1902)
  - Vice President for Academic Affairs- Dr L. F. Maepass, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 1903)
  - Vice President for Administration- Mr S. K. Cassell, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 1904)
  - Vice President, Executive- Dr William J. Keefery, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 1905)
  - Vice President for Finance- Dr William E. E. Lanery, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 1906)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs- Dr James W. Dean, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 1907)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs #2, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 1908)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs #3, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 1909)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs #4, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 1910)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs #5, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 1911)
  - Virginia Academy of Science, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 1912)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 1913)
  - Virginia State College, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 1914)
  - Virginia Tech Athletics Association #1, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 1915)
  - Virginia Tech Athletics Association #2, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 1916)
  - Virginia Tech Student Aid, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 1917)
  - Virginia Experiment Station, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 1918)
  - Visiting Scholar Program, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 1919)
  - V.P.I. Educational Foundation, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 1920)
  - V.P.I. Educational Foundation President's Fund, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 1921)
  - W- Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 1922)
  - Water Resources, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 1923)
  - Wine Awards, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 1924)
  - Y- Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 1925)
  - Y.M.C.A., 1970 (Box 54, Folder 1926)
  - A- Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1927)
  - A.A.U.P., 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1928)
  - A.A.U.W., 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1929)
  - A.B.C. Board, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1930)
  - Accountant- Burke, C.E. #1, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1931)
  - Accountant- Burke, C.E. #2, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1932)
  - Accounting Department, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1933)
  - Accrediting, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1934)
  - Administration Conference (Spring and Fall), 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1935)
  - Administrative Intern, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1936)
  - Admissions and Records Dean M. P. Lacy, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1937)
  - Aerospace Engineering, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1938)
  - Agriculture, College of, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1939)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1940)
  - Agronomy, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1941)
  - Aircraft, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1942)
  - Alumni Association, Gen. #1, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1943)
  - Alumni Association, Gen. #2, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1944)
  - Alumni Contributions, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1945)
  - Alumni President, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1946)
  - American Cancer Society, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1947)
  - American Council on Education, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1948)
  - Anaerobic Laboratory, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1949)
  - Animal Industry Day, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1950)
  - Applications for Positions, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1951)
  - Architecture, College of, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1952)
  - Arts and Sciences, College of, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1953)
  - National Assoc of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1954)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1955)
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities (Southern), 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1956)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1957)
  - Attorney General of Virginia, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1958)
  - Bailey Research Trust, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1959)
  - Basketball, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1960)
  - Bequests, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1961)
  - Biochemistry and Nutrition, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1962)
  - Biology, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1963)
  - Blacksburg, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1964)
  - Board of Visitors, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1965)
  - Board of Visitors #2, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1966)
  - Board of Visitors #3, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1967)
  - Board of Visitors, Copies of Minutes, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1968)
  - Board of Visitors, Correspondence with Members #1, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1969)
  - Board of Visitors, Correspondence with Members #2, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1970)
  - Board of Visitors, Correspondence with Members #3, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1971)
  - Board of Visitors, Correspondence with Members #4, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1972)
  - Board of Visitors, Correspondence with Members #5, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1973)
  - Budget Division, John R. McCutcheson, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1974)
  - Budget Matters, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1975)
  - Building and Grounds, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1976)
  - Business Administration Dept- R.L. King, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1977)
  - Business, College of, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1978)
  - Business Manager, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1979)
  - Capital Outlay Request, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1980)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1981)
  - Cheatham, Julian N., 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1982)
  - Chemical Engineering, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 1983)
  - Chemistry Department, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 1984)
  - Cincinnati Awards, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 1985)
  - Civil Rights, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 1986)
  - Civil Engineering, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 1987)
  - H.E.W. Dyson/Schotta (et al) Related Material, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 1988)
  - Clater, W. Graham, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 1989)
  - Commandant of Cadets, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 1990)
  - Commission on Faculty Affairs, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 1991)
  - Commission on Research and Graduate Studies, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 1992)
  - Commission on Student Affairs, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 1993)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Studies, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 1994)
  - Building Committee, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 1995)
  - Catalog Committee, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 1996)
  - Centennial Committee #1, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 1997)
  - Centennial Committee #2, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 1998)
  - Commencement Exercises, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 1999)
  - Employee Benefits Committee, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 2000)
  - Commencement Committee, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 2001)
  - Computer Committee, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 2002)
  - Committee - Honor Court Review Board, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 2003)
  - Judicial Committee, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 2004)
  - Library Committee, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 2005)
  - Committee- Misc., 1971 (Box 56, Folder 2006)
  - Committee of Patents, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 2007)
  - Scheduling and Registration Committee, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 2008)
  - Scholarships and Student Aid Committee, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 2009)
  - Student Health Services Coordinating Committee, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 2010)
  - Committee to Study Possible Revision of Constitution of University Council, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 2011)
  - Traffic Committee, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 2012)
  - Traffic Appeals Subcommittee, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 2013)
  - Community Colleges, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 2014)
  - Computer Science Dept. Dr G.W. Gorsline, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 2015)
  - Computing Center, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 2016)
  - Consulting, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 2017)
  - Cooperative Program, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 2018)
  - Corps of Cadets, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 2019)
  - Council of President, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 2020)
  - Council of President #2, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 2021)
  - The Counseling Center, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2022)
  - Deans's General, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2023)
  - Dedications, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2024)
  - Development, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2025)
  - Development - W.B. Bell, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2026)
  - Dairy Science, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2027)
  - Dixie - "Pros and Cons", 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2028)
  - Donaldson Brown Center for Continuing Education, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2029)
  - Economics- W.E. Schmedt, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2030)
  - Education, College of, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2031)
  - Editorial Projects for Education, EPE Report, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2032)
  - EDUCOM, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2033)
  - Engineering and Building, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2034)
  - Electrical Engineering, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2035)
  - Engineering, College of, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2036)
  - English Dept., 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2037)
  - Enrollment Statistics, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2038)
  - Entomology, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2039)
  - Environmental Studies, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2040)
  - Esso Education Foundation, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2041)
  - Executive Bulletins "1971", 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2042)
  - Extension Division Dean W.E. Skelton, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2043)
  - Extension Division Dean W.E. Skelton #2, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2044)
  - Extension - General, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2045)
  - Extension Technical Service (State), 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2046)
  - F - Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2047)
  - Faculty Promotions, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2048)
  - Faculty and Christmas List, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2049)
  - Faculty Positions, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2050)
  - Faculty Senate #1, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2051)
  - Faculty Senate #2, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2052)
  - Ferrum Junior College, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2053)
  - Food Science and Technology, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2054)
  - Football, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2055)
  - Ford Foundation, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2056)
  - Foreign Languages, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2057)
  - Forestry and Wildlife, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2058)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2059)
  - Gilbert, David R. - Graduate Student in Physics, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2060)
  - Geological Science, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2061)
  - Glee Club - Kingma, S.G., 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2062)
  - Governor's Day, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2063)
  - Governor of Virginia, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2064)
  - Graduate School, Dean J.W. Bull, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2065)
  - Dr Hahn, Personal #1, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2066)
  - Dr Hahn, Personal #2, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2067)
  - Dr Hahn, Personal #3, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2068)
  - Dr Hahn, Personal #4, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2069)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2070)
  - Higher Education Act of 1965, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2071)
  - Higher Education Facilities Act, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2072)
  - History Dept, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2073)
  - Homecoming, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2074)
  - Home Economics, College of - Dean Laura J. Harper, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2075)
  - Horticulture, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2076)
  - I - Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2077)
  - Industrial Engineering, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2078)
  - Information Services #1, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2079)
  - Information Services #2, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2080)
  - Institutional Research #1, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 2081)
  - Institutional Research #2, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 2082)
  - Invitations Misc #1, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 2083)
  - Invitations Misc #2, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 2084)
  - Invitations Misc #3, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 2085)
  - Invitations - Inaugurations, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 2086)
  - Johnston, J. Ambler, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 2087)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 2088)
  - The Lane Company, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 2089)
  - Law Enforcement Education Program (LEEP), 1971 (Box 59, Folder 2090)
  - Learning Resources Center, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 2091)
  - Legislators - Va General Assembly #1, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 2092)
  - Legislators - Va General Assembly #2, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 2093)
  - Legislators - Va General Assembly #3, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 2094)
  - Legislators - Va General Assembly #4, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 2095)
  - Legislators - Va General Assembly #5, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 2096)
  - Legislators - U.S. Congress #1, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 2097)
  - Legislators - U.S. Congress #2, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 2098)
  - Library, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 2099)
  - M - Miscellaneous #1, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 2100)
  - M - Miscellaneous #2, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 2101)
  - M - Miscellaneous #3, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 2102)
  - M - Miscellaneous #4, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2103)
  - Mathematics, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2104)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2105)
  - Metals and Ceramics, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2106)
  - Military, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2107)
  - Mining Engineering, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2108)
  - Naming Buildings, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2109)
  - National Science Foundation, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2110)
  - National Science Foundation #2, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2111)
  - NDEA, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2112)
  - N - Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2113)
  - Oak Ridge Associated Universities (ORAU), 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2114)
  - Report on the Nuclear Events of Nov 12, 1971, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2115)
  - Organization Charts, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2116)
  - P - Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2117)
  - Pamplin, Robert B., 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2118)
  - Personnel - A.J. Butt, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2119)
  - Personnel - Richmond, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2120)
  - Philippines, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2121)
  - Philosophy and Religion, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2122)
  - Physics, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2123)
  - Political Science, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2124)
  - Physical Education, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2125)
  - Placement, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2126)
  - Plant Pathology and Physiology, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2127)
  - Physical Plant, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2128)
  - Poultry Science, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2129)
  - Psychology, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2130)
  - Purchasing, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2131)
  - Recommendations, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2132)
  - Registrar - R.E. Keller, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2133)
  - Research Corporation, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2134)
  - Requisitions, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2135)
  - Research Division, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2136)
  - Research Division #2, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2137)
  - Reston, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2138)
  - Retirement, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2139)
  - R.O.T.C., 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2140)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2141)
  - Ryland, Walter H. #1, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2142)
  - Ryland, Walter H. #2, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2143)
  - S - Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2144)
  - Salaries, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2145)
  - The Salvation Army, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2146)
  - Savage, Lon K., 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2147)
  - Scholarships and Grants #1, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2148)
  - Scholarships and Grants #2, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2149)
  - Security, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2150)
  - Smithfield, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2151)
  - Sociology, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2152)
  - Proposed New Degree Program, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2153)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2154)
  - Southern Regional Educational Board (SPEB), 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2155)
  - Speaking Engagements, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2156)
  - Speech Material, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2157)
  - Sporn Award, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2158)
  - Staff Meetings, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2159)
  - State Council on Higher Education #1, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2160)
  - State Council on Higher Education #2, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2161)
  - State Council on Higher Education #3, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2162)
  - State Council on Higher Education #4, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2163)
  - Statistics, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2164)
  - Student Budget Board, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2165)
  - Student Affairs - Payne, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2166)
  - Student Forum Board, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2167)
  - Student Government Association #1, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2168)
  - Student Government Association #2, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2169)
  - Student Government Association #3, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2170)
  - Student Housing, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2171)
  - Student - Legislators Forum, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2172)
  - Student Letters To and From #1, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2173)
  - Student Letters To and From #2, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2174)
  - Student Letters Other #1, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2175)
  - Student Letters Other #2, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2176)
  - Student Organizations #1, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2177)
  - Student Organizations #2, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2178)
  - Student Publications Board, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2179)
  - Student Services - Brown, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2180)
  - Student Residence Programs (Harder), 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2181)
  - Student Union, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2182)
  - Subscription, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2183)
  - Summer School Program, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2184)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2185)
  - TIAA-CREF, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2186)
  - TRW, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2187)
  - University Council #1, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2188)
  - University Council #2, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2189)
  - University Council #3, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2190)
  - University Council #4, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 2191)
  - University Services and Auxiliary Enterprises, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 2192)
  - University Professors, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 2193)
  - Upward Bound, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 2194)
  - V Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 2195)
  - VALC (Virginia Advisory Legislative Council), 1971 (Box 63, Folder 2196)
  - Veterinary Science, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 2197)
  - Vice President Academic Affairs #1, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 2198)
  - Vice President Academic Affairs #2, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 2199)
  - Vice President Administration, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 2200)
  - Executive Vice President, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 2201)
  - Confidential- Dr McKeefery, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 2202)
  - Vice President - Finance, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 2203)
  - Vice President Student Affairs #1, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 2204)
  - Vice President Student Affairs #2, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 2205)
  - Vice President Student Affairs #3, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 2206)
  - Vice President Student Affairs #4, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 2207)
  - Vice President Student Affairs #5, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 2208)
  - Virginia Academy of Science, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 2209)
  - Virginia Academy of Science: Visiting Scientist Program, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 2210)
  - Virginia Department of Agriculture, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 2211)
  - Virginia State Chamber Of Commerce, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 2212)
  - Virginia Tech Athletic Association #1, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 2213)
  - Virginia Tech Athletic Association #2, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 2214)
  - VPI Ed. Foundation - President Fund, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 2215)
  - VPI Education Foundation, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 2216)
  - Visiting School Program, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 2217)
  - Va Truck Expense Station, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 2218)
  - Va Tech Student Aid Assoc., 1971 (Box 64, Folder 2219)
  - VPI Special Committee, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 2220)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 2221)
  - Wine Awards, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 2222)
  - Water Resources Research Center, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 2223)
  - YMCA, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 2224)
  - AAUW, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 2225)
  - A Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 2226)
  - AAUP, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 2227)
  - Accounting Department, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 2228)
  - Accounting Burruss Hall, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 2229)
  - Administrative Intern, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 2230)
  - Administrative Conference (Fall), 1972 (Box 64, Folder 2231)
  - Administrative Records #1, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 2232)
  - Administrative Records #2, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 2233)
  - Aerospace Engineering, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 2234)
  - Agriculture, College of, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 2235)
  - College of Agriculture and Life Sciences #2, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 2236)
  - Agriculture Economics, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 2237)
  - Agriculture Engineering, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 2238)
  - Agronomy, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 2239)
  - Airport, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 2240)
  - Aircraft, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 2241)
  - Alumni Association Gen #1, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 2242)
- Series VI, 1972-1973
  - Alumni Association Gen #2, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2243)
  - Alumni Association Gen #3, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2244)
  - Alumni Association President, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2245)
  - Alumni Contributions, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2246)
  - Alumni Distinguished Professor (Dr Bloss), 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2247)
  - American Cancer Society #1, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2248)
  - American Cancer Society #2, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2249)
  - American Council On Education, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2250)
  - Anaerobic Laboratory, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2251)
  - Animal Science Department, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2252)
  - Applications For Positions #1, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2253)
  - Applications For Positions #2, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2254)
  - Architecture, College of, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2255)
  - Arts and Sciences, College of, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2256)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2257)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2258)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2259)
  - Southern Association of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2260)
  - Attorney General of Virginia, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2261)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2262)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2263)
  - Bailey Research Trust, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2264)
  - Basketball, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2265)
  - Bequests, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2266)
  - Biology Department, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2267)
  - Blacksburg, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2268)
  - Board of Visitors, Copies of Minutes #1, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2269)